A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.2, Series 100 International - Series 253 Washington FA387a
Rockefeller Archive Center
- United States, 1929-1977; 200; 113 box(es)
  - United States - Nursing, 1947-1970; 200.C; 2.4 Cubic Feet; 6 __Boxes __2.4 cubic feet
    - Columbia University - Nursing Education, 1951-1961 (Box 166, Folder 1511)
    - Columbia University - Nursing Education, 1951-1961 (Box 166, Folder 1512)
    - Columbia University - Nursing Education - Supplemental Material, 1954-1955, 1958 (Box 166, Folder 1513)
    - Columbia University - Nursing Education - Supplemental Material, 1954-1955, 1958 (Box 166, Folder 1514)
    - Columbia University - Nursing Education - Supplemental Material, 1954-1955, 1958 (Box 166, Folder 1515)
    - Columbia University - Nursing Education - Supplemental Material, 1956, 1959 (Box 167, Folder 1516)
    - Columbia University - Nursing Seminar, 1958-1960 (Box 167, Folder 1517)
    - Downstate Medical Center - Cavero, Carmela - (Travel, Columbia), 1966 (Box 167, Folder 1518)
    - Duke University - Graduate Program, 1957-1964 (Box 167, Folder 1519)
    - Duke University - Graduate Program, 1957-1964 (Box 167, Folder 1520)
    - Harvard University - Tancock, Catherine B. - (Travel Grant, N. Ireland), 1959-1960 (Box 167, Folder 1521)
    - Howard, Anna Taylor - (Travel, Nigeria), 1968 (Box 167, Folder 1522)
    - Massachusetts General Hospital - Sleeper, Ruth - (Travel Grant, N. Ireland), 1959 (Box 167, Folder 1523)
    - Mills, Mary L. - (Tuition, Johns Hopkins University), 1957 (Box 167, Folder 1524)
    - National Committee for the Improvement of Nursing Services, 1949-1951 (Box 167, Folder 1525)
    - National Committee for the Improvement of Nursing Services, 1949-1951 (Box 167, Folder 1526)
    - National Committee for the Improvement of Nursing Services, 1949-1951 (Box 167, Folder 1527)
    - National Fund for Graduate Nursing Education, 1958-1960 (Box 167, Folder 1528)
    - National Fund for Graduate Nursing Education, 1958-1960 (Box 167, Folder 1529)
    - National League for Nursing, Inc. - Practical Nurses Leadership Training, 1957-1959 (Box 168, Folder 1530)
    - National Nursing Accrediting Service, 1950-1957 (Box 168, Folder 1531)
    - National Nursing Accrediting Service, 1950-1957 (Box 168, Folder 1532)
    - National Nursing Accrediting Service, 1950-1957 (Box 168, Folder 1533)
    - National Nursing Council - Brown, Esther L. - ("Nursing for the Future"), 1947-1950, 1958 (Box 168, Folder 1534)
    - National Nursing Council - Brown, Esther L. - ("Nursing for the Future"), 1947-1950, 1958 (Box 168, Folder 1535)
    - National Nursing Council - Brown, Esther L. - ("Nursing for the Future"), 1947-1950, 1958 (Box 168, Folder 1536)
    - New York Hospital - Public Health Study, 1958-January 1959 (Box 168, Folder 1537)
    - New York Hospital - Public Health Study, 1958-January 1959 (Box 168, Folder 1538)
    - New York Hospital - Public Health Study, February 1959-1962 (Box 169, Folder 1539)
    - New York Hospital - Public Health Study, February 1959-1962 (Box 169, Folder 1540)
    - New York Hospital - Public Health Study, February 1959-1962 (Box 169, Folder 1541)
    - Pan American Health Organization - La Motte, Jeanne - (Nursing and Midwifery), 1959-1960 (Box 169, Folder 1542)
    - Planned Parenthood Federation of America, Inc. - Nursing Survey - (Martin, Ruth, Curriculum Content), 1964-1967 (Box 169, Folder 1543)
    - Planned Parenthood Federation of America, Inc. - Nursing Survey - (Martin, Ruth, Curriculum Content), 1964-1967 (Box 169, Folder 1544)
    - Radcliffe College - (Educational Concept of Program with Massachusetts General Hospital), 1955-1958 (Box 169, Folder 1545)
    - Simmons College - (Graduate Program with Harvard School of Public Health), 1952-1961 (Box 169, Folder 1546)
    - Tulane University - McGill, Cloace F. - (Travel Grant, Midwifery), 1960-1961 (Box 170, Folder 1547)
    - United States - Health, Education & Welfare - Taylor, Ruth G. - (Travel Grant, South America), 1960-1961 (Box 170, Folder 1548)
    - University of California-Los Angeles - Doctoral Program, 1957-1960 (Box 170, Folder 1549)
    - University of California-Los Angeles - Hassenplug, Lulu W. - (Travel Grant, Asia), 1958-1959 (Box 170, Folder 1550)
    - University of California-San Francisco - Harms, Mary - (Travel Grant, Japan), 1960-1962 (Box 170, Folder 1551)
    - University of California-San Francisco - Nahm, Helen - (Travel Grant), 1961-1963 (Box 170, Folder 1552)
    - University of Chicago - Pediatrics - (Blake, Florence G., Study of), 1959-1961, 1963 (Box 170, Folder 1553)
    - University of Chicago - Pediatrics - (Blake, Florence G., Study of), 1959-1961, 1963 (Box 170, Folder 1554)
    - University of Florida - Nursing Exchange (Universidad del Valle, Colombia), 1965-1969 (Box 170, Folder 1555)
    - University of Florida - Nursing Exchange (Universidad del Valle, Colombia), 1965-1969 (Box 170, Folder 1556)
    - University of Minnesota - Dunning, Frances E. - (Travel Grant, South America), 1959 (Box 170, Folder 1557)
    - University of Missouri - Harrison, Virginia H. - (Travel, U.S., Nurse Education), 1949-1954 (Box 170, Folder 1558)
    - Visiting Nurse Association of Rochester - Phillips, Elisabeth C. - (Travel, Scandinavia), 1951-1953 (Box 170, Folder 1559)
    - Wayne State University - Bower, Irene - (Travel Grant, Europe), 1960-1961 (Box 170, Folder 1560)
    - Wayne State University - Cooperative Program, 1963-1964 (Box 171, Folder 1561)
    - Wayne State University - Cooperative Program, 1965 (Box 171, Folder 1562)
    - Wayne State University - Cooperative Program, 1967-1968 (Box 171, Folder 1563)
    - Wayne State University - Faville, Katharine E., 1962-1963 (Box 171, Folder 1564)
    - Wayne State University - Fischer, Lorene H., 1960-1962, 1966-1967 (Box 171, Folder 1565)
    - Wayne State University - Hopkins, Marilyn A., 1961-1962 (Box 171, Folder 1566)
    - Wayne State University - Visits, 1957-1960 (Box 171, Folder 1567)
    - Wayne State University - Visits, 1961 (Box 171, Folder 1568)
    - Wayne State University - Keresey, Elinor P., 1955-1957 (Box 171, Folder 1569)
  - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1929-1974; 200.D; 82 box(es)
    (Research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture.)
    - Agriculture and Mechanical College of Texas - Animal Nutrition - (Ellis, William C.), 1961-1967 (Box 171, Folder 1570)
    - Agriculture and Mechanical College of Texas - Animal Nutrition - (Ellis, William C.), 1961-1967 (Box 171, Folder 1571)
    - Agriculture and Mechanical College of Texas - Evatt, Nathan S. - (Travel Grant), 1963-1964 (Box 172, Folder 1572)
    - Agriculture and Mechanical College of Texas - Oat Study, 1963-1967 (Box 172, Folder 1573)
    - Agriculture and Mechanical College of Texas - Oat Study, 1963-1967 (Box 172, Folder 1574)
    - Agriculture and Mechanical College of Texas - Plant Science, 1956-1963 (Box 172, Folder 1575)
    - Agriculture and Mechanical College of Texas - Plant Science, 1956-1963 (Box 172, Folder 1576)
    - Agriculture and Mechanical University of Texas - Escriva, Jose L., 1966-1967 (Box 172, Folder 1577)
    - Agriculture and Mechanical University of Texas - Visits - (Travel Grants - Maurer, Fred D. and Livingston, Charles W., Jr.), 1965-1969 (Box 172, Folder 1578)
    - Agriculture and Mechanical University of Texas - Visits - (Travel Grants - Maurer, Fred D. and Livingston, Charles W., Jr.), 1965-1969 (Box 172, Folder 1579)
    - Alabama Polytechnic Institute - Nematology, 1953-1959 (Box 172, Folder 1580)
    - Albert, Fritz A., 1959-1960 (Box 172, Folder 1581)
    - Alcorn Agricultural and Mechanical College - State Development, 1968 (Box 172, Folder 1582)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science - Arid Lands Symposium, 1954 (Box 172, Folder 1583)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science - Arid Land Symposium, 1955 (Box 173, Folder 1584)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science - Gordon Research Conferences, 1950-1960 (Box 173, Folder 1585)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science - Gordon Research Conferences, 1950-1960 (Box 173, Folder 1586)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science - Gordon Research Conferences, 1950-1960 (Box 173, Folder 1587)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science - Program Planning, 1951-1954 (Box 173, Folder 1588)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science - World Food Symposium, 1968-1969 (Box 173, Folder 1589)
    - American Forage and Grassland Council - Conference, 1968-1970 (Box 173, Folder 1590)
    - American Institute of Biological Sciences - Conference, 1959-1960 (Box 173, Folder 1591)
    - American Museum of Natural History - Ecology - (Schneirla, Ted C. and Lienau, Carl C.), 1951-1957 (Box 173, Folder 1592)
    - American Museum of Natural History - Kurten, Bjorn - (Visiting Scholar), 1959 (Box 173, Folder 1593)
    - American Phytopathological Society - Fungus Symposium, 1964-1965 (Box 174, Folder 1594)
    - American Phytopathological Society - Latin American Conference, 1953-1954 (Box 174, Folder 1595)
    - American Phytopathological Society - Symposia, 1956-1959 (Box 174, Folder 1596)
    - American Psychological Association - Evolution of Behavior, 1953-1957 (Box 174, Folder 1597)
    - American Society of Agronomy - Publication - ("Agronomy in the Americas"), 1963-1965 (Box 174, Folder 1598)
    - American-Soviet Science Society, 1946-1958 (Box 174, Folder 1599)
    - American Veterinary Medical Association - Symposium - (Veterinary Education), 1964-1966 (Box 174, Folder 1600)
    - Andrews, Frederick N. - (Travel Grant), 1961-1962 (Box 174, Folder 1601)
    - Association of State Universities - Latin American Development, 1962-1963 (Box 174, Folder 1602)
    - Association of State Universities - Latin American Development, 1962-1963 (Box 174, Folder 1603)
    - Association of State Universities - Latin American Development, 1964-1966 (Box 175, Folder 1604)
    - Auburn University - Fisheries, 1965-1972 (Box 175, Folder 1605)
    - Auburn University - Fisheries, 1965-1972 (Box 175, Folder 1606)
    - Auburn University - Fisheries, 1965-1972 (Box 175, Folder 1607)
    - Auburn University - Fisheries - Supplemental Material, 1967-1969 (Box 175, Folder 1608)
    - Auburn University - Fisheries - Supplemental Material, 1967-1969 (Box 175, Folder 1609)
    - Auburn University - Fisheries - Supplemental Material, 1967-1969 (Box 175, Folder 1610)
    - Auburn University - Swingle, Homer S. - (Travel Grant), 1960-1962 (Box 176, Folder 1611)
    - Austin State College - Gibson, William W. - (Travel Grant), 1965-1966 (Box 176, Folder 1612)
    - Bates, Quentin - (Travel Grant), 1953 (Box 176, Folder 1613)
    - Bishop Museum - Yen, Douglas E. - (Travel Grant), 1967 (Box 176, Folder 1614)
    - Blount, Roswell C. - (Travel Grant), 1963-1964 (Box 176, Folder 1615)
    - Boston University - Immunology - (Boyd, William C.), 1942-1951 (Box 176, Folder 1616)
    - Boy Scouts of America - Conservation, 1955-1960 (Box 176, Folder 1617)
    - Boy Scouts of America - Conservation - (Supplemental Material), 1956-1960 (Box 176, Folder 1618)
    - Boy Scouts of America - Conservation - (Supplemental Material), 1956-1960 (Box 176, Folder 1619)
    - Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research - Fungi, 1956-1960 (Box 176, Folder 1620)
    - Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research - Fungi, 1956-1960 (Box 176, Folder 1621)
    - Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research - Fungi, 1961-1963 (Box 177, Folder 1622)
    - Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research - Magdoff, Beatrice S. - (Travel Grant), 1957 (Box 177, Folder 1623)
    - Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research - Plant Growth Conference, 1958-1961 (Box 177, Folder 1624)
    - Brooklyn Botanic Garden - Avery, George S. - (Travel Grant), 1950, 1955 (Box 177, Folder 1625)
    - Brown University - Biology, 1958-1962 (Box 177, Folder 1626)
    - Brown University - Biology - Reprints (Box 177, Folder 1627)
    - Brown University - Sachs, Abraham - (Travel Grant), 1951-1953 (Box 177, Folder 1628)
    - California Institute of Technology - Biology and Chemistry Conference, 1952-1954 (Box 177, Folder 1629)
    - California Institute of Technology - Corey, Robert S., 1955 (Box 177, Folder 1630)
    - California Institute of Technology - Geochemistry - (Travel Grant), 1954-1955 (Box 177, Folder 1631)
    - California Institute of Technology - Plant Physiology, 1951-1966 (Box 177, Folder 1632)
    - California Institute of Technology - Plant Physiology, 1951-1966 (Box 177, Folder 1633)
    - California Institute of Technology - Plant Physiology, 1951-1966 (Box 177, Folder 1634)
    - California Institute of Technology - Soriano, Alberto, 1951-1952 (Box 177, Folder 1635)
    - Carleton College - Biology, 1959-1961 (Box 178, Folder 1636)
    - Citrus Experiment Station - Fuertes-Polo, Celia, 1961-1962 (Box 178, Folder 1637)
    - Clemson Agricultural College - Clover Fungi, 1960-1963 (Box 178, Folder 1638)
    - Clemson Agricultural College - Entomology - (Weather Recording Equipment), 1959-1963 (Box 178, Folder 1639)
    - Cohn, Melvin - (Travel Grant), 1955-1956 (Box 178, Folder 1640)
    - Colorado State University - Husseini, Karim K. - (Travel Grant), 1966 (Box 178, Folder 1641)
    - Columbia University - Biochemistry - Dische, Zacharias, 1951-1954 (Box 178, Folder 1642)
    - Columbia University - Biochemistry - Shemin, David, 1948-1954 (Box 178, Folder 1643)
    - Columbia University - Botany, 1949-1955 (Box 178, Folder 1644)
    - Columbia University - Chargaff, Erwin - (Travel Grant), 1958-1960 (Box 178, Folder 1645)
    - Columbia University - Disadvantaged Students Program, 1970-1973 (Box 178, Folder 1646)
    - Columbia University - Ecology - Sternberg, Hilgard O., 1964-1966 (Box 178, Folder 1647)
    - Columbia University - Enzyme Chemistry, 1956-1960 (Box 178, Folder 1648)
    - Columbia University - Genetics - Appleyard, Raymond, 1959-1961 (Box 178, Folder 1649)
    - Columbia University - Genetics - Dobzhansky, Theodosius, 1946-1963 (Box 178, Folder 1650)
    - Columbia University - Immuno-Chemistry - (Heidelberger, Michael), 1944-1956 (Box 179, Folder 1651)
    - Columbia University - Immuno-Chemistry - (Heidelberger, Michael), 1944-1956 (Box 179, Folder 1652)
    - Columbia University - Language and Communications - (Lotz, John), 1951-1954 (Box 179, Folder 1653)
    - Columbia University - Marine Biology, 1953-1962, 1970-1974 (Box 179, Folder 1654)
    - Columbia University - Marine Biology, 1953-1962, 1970-1974 (Box 179, Folder 1655)
    - Columbia University - Marine Biology, 1953-1962, 1970-1974 (Box 179, Folder 1656)
    - Columbia University - Marine Biology, 1953-1962, 1970-1974 (Box 179, Folder 1657)
    - Columbia University - Marine Biology - Supplemental Material, 1972 (Box 179, Folder 1658)
    - Columbia University - Marine Biology - Supplemental Material (Box 180, Folder 1659)
    - Columbia University - Rittenberg, David, 1953-1954 (Box 180, Folder 1660)
    - Columbia University - Selenium - (Trelease, Sam F.), 1943, 1948-1954 (Box 180, Folder 1661)
    - Columbia University - Tissue Culture Index - (Publication-"Bibliography of the Research of Tissue Culture, 1900-1950"), 1951-1954 (Box 180, Folder 1662)
    - Columbia University - Yukawa, Hideki, 1949-1951 (Box 180, Folder 1663)
    - Connecticut Agriculture Experiment Station - Diamond, Albert E. - (Travel Grant), 1962-1963 (Box 180, Folder 1664)
    - Connecticut Agriculture Experiment Station - Horsfall, James G. - (Travel Grant), 1961-1962 (Box 180, Folder 1665)
    - Conservation Foundation, 1947-1950 (Box 180, Folder 1666)
    - Conservation Foundation, 1947-1950 (Box 180, Folder 1667)
    - Conservation Foundation, 1947-1950 (Box 180, Folder 1668)
    - Conservation Foundation, 1947-1950 (Box 180, Folder 1669)
    - Conservation Foundation, 1951-1961 (Box 181, Folder 1670)
    - Conservation Foundation, 1951-1961 (Box 181, Folder 1671)
    - Conservation Foundation, 1951-1961 (Box 181, Folder 1672)
    - Conservation Foundation, 1951-1961 (Box 181, Folder 1673)
    - Conservation Foundation, 1951-1961 (Box 181, Folder 1674)
    - Conservation Foundation, 1951-1961 (Box 181, Folder 1675)
    - Conservation Foundation - African Ecology, 1959-1961 (Box 181, Folder 1676)
    - Conservation Foundation - Pesticide Project, 1957-1963 (Box 181, Folder 1677)
    - Conservation Foundation - Seminars, 1964-1966 (Box 181, Folder 1678)
    - Cornell University - Agriculture, 1952-1964 (Box 182, Folder 1679)
    - Cornell University - Agriculture, 1952-1964 (Box 182, Folder 1680)
    - Cornell University - Agriculture - Reports, 1958-1961 (Box 182, Folder 1681)
    - Cornell University - Agriculture - Orientation Program, 1960-1968 (Box 182, Folder 1682)
    - Cornell University - Agriculture - Orientation Program, 1960-1968 (Box 182, Folder 1683)
    - Cornell University - Agriculture - Orientation Program, 1960-1968 (Box 182, Folder 1684)
    - Cornell University - Biological Exchange Program, 1966-1969 (Box 182, Folder 1685)
    - Cornell University - Biological Exchange Program, 1970-1972 (Box 183, Folder 1686)
    - Cornell University - Botany - (Fairbrothers, David E.), 1952-1954 (Box 183, Folder 1687)
    - Cornell University - Boynton, Damon - (Travel Grant), 1958-1959 (Box 183, Folder 1688)
    - Cornell University - Cline, Marlin G. - (Travel Grant), 1958-1959 (Box 183, Folder 1689)
    - Cornell University - Cline, Marlin G. - Diary, 1958 (Box 183, Folder 1690)
    - Cornell University - Crowden, Loy V. - (Travel Grant), 1964-1965 (Box 183, Folder 1691)
    - Cornell University - Electron Microscope, 1949-1955 (Box 183, Folder 1692)
    - Cornell University - Gagni, Arsenio, 1968 (Box 183, Folder 1693)
    - Cornell University - Genetics - (Davis, Bernard D.), 1950-1954 (Box 183, Folder 1694)
    - Cornell University - Gillespie, James H. - (Travel Grant), 1963-1964 (Box 183, Folder 1695)
    - Cornell University - Hogue, Douglas E. - (Travel Grant), 1964 (Box 183, Folder 1696)
    - Cornell University - Hot-Humid Tropics Symposium, 1965-1967 (Box 183, Folder 1697)
    - Cornell University - Jensen, Neal F., 1968 (Box 183, Folder 1698)
    - Cornell University - Johnson, Al A. - (Travel Grant), 1962 (Box 183, Folder 1699)
    - Cornell University - Labadan, Marro M. - (Travel Grant), 1966 (Box 183, Folder 1700)
    - Cornell University - Merrill, William G. - (Travel Grant), 1965-1966 (Box 183, Folder 1701)
    - Cornell University - Nesheim, Malden C. - (Travel Grant), 1964-1965 (Box 183, Folder 1702)
    - Cornell University - Ngere, Livinius, 1969-1970 (Box 183, Folder 1703)
    - Cornell University - Plaisted, Robert L., 1963-1965, 1969-1971 (Box 183, Folder 1704)
    - Cornell University - Plant Research, 1953-1954, 1957-1965 (Box 184, Folder 1705)
    - Cornell University - Plant Research, 1953-1954, 1957-1965 (Box 184, Folder 1706)
    - Cornell University - Plant Research, 1953-1954, 1957-1965 (Box 184, Folder 1707)
    - Cornell University - Plant Research, 1953-1954, 1957-1965 (Box 184, Folder 1708)
    - Cornell University - Pond, Wilson G. - (Travel Grant), 1963-1964 (Box 184, Folder 1709)
    - Cornell University - Tyler, Leon J. - (Travel Grant), 1959-1961 (Box 184, Folder 1710)
    - Cornell University - Veterinary Visits - (Travel Grant), 1968 (Box 184, Folder 1711)
    - Cornell University - Wimsatt, William A. - (Travel Grant), 1968 (Box 184, Folder 1712)
    - Cornell University - Wright, Madison J. - (Travel Grant), 1965-1966 (Box 184, Folder 1713)
    - Cornell University - Young, Robert J. - (Travel Grant), 1965-1966 (Box 184, Folder 1714)
    - Cox, Gertrude M. - (Travel Grant), 1954-1955 (Box 184, Folder 1715)
    - Crop Quality Council - Hayden, Eugene B., Jr. - (Travel Grant), 1965-1967 (Box 184, Folder 1716)
    - Dartmouth College - Physiology, 1951-1959 (Box 185, Folder 1717)
    - Dartmouth College - Physiology - Reprints, 1954-1956 (Box 185, Folder 1718)
    - Duke University - Forestry, 1960-1966 (Box 185, Folder 1719)
    - Duke University - Forestry, 1960-1966 (Box 185, Folder 1720)
    - Duke University - Handler, Philip - (Travel Grant), 1955-1956 (Box 185, Folder 1721)
    - Duke University - Harrar, E.S., 1966 (Box 185, Folder 1722)
    - Duke University - Tropical Forestry Conference, 1964-1968 (Box 185, Folder 1723)
    - Efferson, J. Norman, 1960 (Box 185, Folder 1724)
    - Emory University - Enzyme Research, 1951-1957 (Box 185, Folder 1725)
    - Entomological Society of America - De Wilde, J., 1961-1962 (Box 185, Folder 1726)
    - Entomological Society of America - Visits, 1960-1961 (Box 185, Folder 1727)
    - Entomological Society of America - Weiser, Jaroslav, 1958-1960 (Box 185, Folder 1728)
    - Errington, Paul, 1962 (Box 185, Folder 1729)
    - Estes Park Center for Research and Education - Food Policy, 1964-1966 (Box 186, Folder 1730)
    - Estes Park Center for Research and Education - Food Policy, 1964-1966 (Box 186, Folder 1731)
    - Estes Park Center for Research and Education - Food Policy, 1964-1966 (Box 186, Folder 1732)
    - Estes Park Center for Research and Education - Food Policy - Supplemental Material, 1965 (Box 186, Folder 1733)
    - Estes Park Center for Research and Education - Food Policy - Supplemental Material, 1965 (Box 186, Folder 1734)
    - Estes Park Center for Research and Education - Food Policy - Supplemental Material, 1965 (Box 186, Folder 1735)
    - Estes Park Center for Research and Education - Food Policy - Supplemental Material, 1965 (Box 186, Folder 1736)
    - Fernow, Karl H. - (Travel Grant), 1965 (Box 186, Folder 1737)
    - Florida State University - Oceanography, 1955-1957 (Box 187, Folder 1738)
    - Gaulden, Mary E. - (Experimental Biology--Cytology), 1955-1956 (Box 187, Folder 1739)
    - Genetics Society of America - (Golden Jubilee Meeting), 1950-1951 (Box 187, Folder 1740)
    - Genetics Society of America - Stubbe, Hans - (Travel Grant), 1964-1966 (Box 187, Folder 1741)
    - George Washington University - Biological Sciences Communication Project, 1963-1967 (Box 187, Folder 1742)
    - George Washington University - Biological Sciences Communication Project - Maize and Wheat, 1966-1971 (Box 187, Folder 1743)
    - George Washington University - Biological Sciences Communication Project - Maize and Wheat, 1966-1971 (Box 187, Folder 1744)
    - George Washington University - Biological Sciences Communication Project - Maize and Wheat, 1966-1971 (Box 187, Folder 1745)
    - George Washington University - Biological Sciences Communication Project - Maize and Wheat, 1966-1971 (Box 187, Folder 1746)
    - George Washington University - Biological Sciences Communication Project - Maize and Wheat, 1966-1971 (Box 187, Folder 1747)
    - George Washington University - Biological Sciences Communication Project - Sorghum and Millet, 1963-1968 (Box 188, Folder 1748)
    - George Washington University - Biological Sciences Communication Project - Sorghum and Millet, 1963-1968 (Box 188, Folder 1749)
    - George Washington University - Biological Sciences Communication Project - Sorghum and Millet, 1963-1968 (Box 188, Folder 1750)
    - George Washington University - Biological Sciences Communication Project - Sorghum and Millet, 1963-1968 (Box 188, Folder 1751)
    - Gulf Coast Research Laboratory - Marine Biology - (Abbott, Walter), 1965-1969 (Box 188, Folder 1752)
    - Hagan, Robert M. - (Travel Grant), 1955-1957 (Box 188, Folder 1753)
    - Hanson, Lester E., 1959 (Box 188, Folder 1754)
    - Harris, Lorin E., 1956-1960 (Box 188, Folder 1755)
    - Harvard University - Bacteriology, 1948-1953 (Box 188, Folder 1756)
    - Harvard University - Biophysical Chemistry - (Doty, Paul M.), 1950-1954 (Box 188, Folder 1757)